<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" >
<channel>
<title>Firefox Private Browsing Mode, Torbutton, and Fingerprinting</title>
<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/</link>
<description>The Tor Blog</description>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 1</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_1/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_1/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 07:03:07 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:07Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity to bash Mozilla (Googlezilla) and Google!!!!! Well, yeah they&#39;re almost the same thing!!! haha!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Chrome is just a trash browser, it belongs to the Google&#39;s idea to conquer the world, and it&#39;s a piece of the imperialistic way of Google to do things!!! Expanding itself everywhere and controlling the others!!!!! Google is the same multinational company who said to leave China, then it changed idea, then it changed idea again and again... and if you read the news of yesterday, it seems like Google doesn&#39;t care the least bit, and it&#39;s okay to accept censorship because Google is well-willing to support everyone&#39;s censorship!!!! Yeah, google is a multinational company, it has shareholders to make happy!! Google doesn&#39;t care about anyone&#39;s privacy nor freedom!!!! Google is the leader of online advertising too!! It&#39;s very interested in tracking users!!!!!!!!!!!!! Quit mistaking Google with a good Samaritan!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
There is also this thing about &quot;Google Chrome&quot; and &quot;Google/Mozilla Firefox&quot;!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
Mozilla has been corrupted by Google&#39;s donations (i like to call them &quot;bribes&quot;!!!!). So, you&#39;ve got in Firefox as the default search engine, the web search engine of the most anti-privacy company ever (GOOGLE!!, look at the report of privacy international) and if you look at the search-plugins of Firefox you may as well notice tracking parameters in the queries to send to google!!!!! (client=firefox-a &amp;amp; client=firefox &amp;amp; rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official) Anyway, it&#39;s AMO (addons.mozilla.org) the worst piece of Mozilla, it&#39;s the most corrupted!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
Firefox is linked to Google, and of course Chrome is linked to Google too!!! The effect of Google&#39;s invasion is very easy to notice!!!! So, it&#39;s like saying that Google has TWO browsers!!!!!!! Its Chrome and controls Firefox!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
You don&#39;t have to wonder why the bug &quot;280661 - SOCKS proxy server connection timeout hard-coded&quot; is five years old and nobody wanted to patch it yet!!!!! If that bug had been solved, you could use Firefox+TOR without needing an HTTP proxy (like polipo!!) Chris wrote a patch, but Mozilla didn&#39;t yet merged it with the main source code of firefox!!! Because, they asked for somebody to review the code... but at Mozilla nobody is interested!!! Yeah, nobody at Mozilla has time to spend to review a patch they&#39;re not interested in!!!!!!!!!!! At the same time, don&#39;t forget it&#39;s a five years old bug, Firefox evolved into a Bloatware!!! For instance, you&#39;ve got Firefox supporting useless and very ugly &quot;PERSONAS&quot;... and at the same time, the useful patch to improve SOCKETS has been forgotten, and at the same time Google managed to release its own light web-browser!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
It&#39;s sadly funny, if you think that firefox born as a light version of SeaMonkey!!!!!! (former Application Suite, former Netscape)!!&lt;br /&gt;
For Mozilla PERSONAS were the priority and patching the SOCKETS has not been done yet!!!!! Chris was forced to write test-case applications, and i think he was hopeful that to be the last step before having his patch published, merged together with the main source code of FIREFOX!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Mozilla has recently added to Firefox a new feature to run Plugins as separated processes!!! well, yeah, i can say that one to be a nice improvement and much more useful than Personas, but again, that improvement brought into Firefox a lot of bugs, one of which doesn&#39;t allow you anymore to build Firefox removing the support for plugins!!!!! Yeah, Chris had to write a testing tool just to waste some of his time, on the other hand non-working and useless patches and features went through reviews and accepted in &lt;strong&gt;no time!!!!&lt;/strong&gt; with the main and only consequence, that one of the most useful options to build firefox, to have it much more stable than ever and much more privacy-oriented, doesn&#39;t work anymore!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! (https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=574950 they wrote &quot;resolved&quot;, but it hasn&#39;t been resolved yet!!!). Surely, if this makes feel you happy, you&#39;ve got ugly personas to look at!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ahah!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
Neither Mozilla (Googlezilla) nor Google, are for real interested in their users privacy!!!!!! AMO is continuously tracking users via the addons system, google wants to track you due to Analytics/Adsense/etc... Mozilla doesn&#39;t care about useful improvements for Firefox and useful patches, because all they&#39;re doing is to turn Firefox into a non-working bloatware!!! And Google began to spread its own web browser!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
Before the &quot;Anonymous Browsing Mode&quot; it would be better for Mozilla to remove all the Google&#39;s fluffs from Firefox and to apply to it the real useful patches!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Because nobody cares about new features in an impaired browser!!!!!!!!!! Also, it would be better for the TorProject to leave alone google!!!!the evilest multinational company ever!!!! It sounds Google, it sounds familiar, but it&#39;s what&#39;s going to betray you!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bye!!!!!!!! ~bee!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 2</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_2/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_2/</link>

	<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 07:03:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:08Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Finally &lt;strong&gt;A STEP AHEAD for MOZILLA!!!!&lt;/strong&gt; (and this is an important one!!!!!!!!!!!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All Firefox versions &amp;gt;= 3.6.4 build again!!!!!!!!! There is a workaround to build firefox without the plugins support in these recent versions!!! You need, also, to disable the plugins isolation!!!!! It&#39;s possible adding &quot;--disable-ipc&quot; to the configure command!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
« https://bugzilla.mozilla.org/show_bug.cgi?id=574950 »&lt;br /&gt;
Well, yeah, i&#39;ve also updated FireFox in Factorbee!!!! Tested it, and everything works!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bye!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
~bee!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 3</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_3/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_3/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:03:09 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:09Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>What about bug #280661? Any hope to have it fixed any time soon?
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 4</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_4/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_4/</link>

	<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 07:03:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:10Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Another update!!!!!!!! About google this time!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/business/10566318.stm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;«The Chinese government has renewed Google&#39;s licence to operate in China»&lt;br /&gt;
«The licence renewal is key to Google. Losing business in China, which already has more internet users than any other country despite relatively low penetration, could harm the company&#39;s future growth prospects.»&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Haha!!! Well, at least shareholders are happy!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
Of course, Google&#39;s being an evil multinational company always ready to betray their promises and collaborating with pro-censorship governments, like the chinese gov, doesn&#39;t stop the TorProject to use the Google Summer of Code projects!!!!!!!!!(just to name one!!) hah!!! Misconceptions!?! naw!! It&#39;s surely coherent, making a tool to fight censorship, introducing evasion mechanisms like &quot;bridges&quot; made on purpose against the china&#39;s great firewall... and then collaborating with &lt;strong&gt;multinational companies&lt;/strong&gt; like Google!!!!!!! (allied, or to say the least &lt;em&gt;subjected&lt;/em&gt;, to the pro-censorship folk!!!!!!!!!!!) !!!!!!!!!!!! lol!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Well, that&#39;s the result of &quot;capitalism&quot;!!!!!! and funnily, it has the same result of Soviet communism!!!!! haha!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bye!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
~bee!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 5</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_5/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_5/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 07:03:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:11Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>Good luck with the development, its a shame that there are so many barriers to great plug ins. 
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 6</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_6/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_6/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 07:03:12 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:12Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks Mike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your efforts are appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 7</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_7/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_7/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 07:03:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:13Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>Fingerprinting has been an issue more and more with Tor. I hope that it can be resolved.
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>phobos: Comment 8</title>
	<dcterms:creator>phobos</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_8/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_8/</link>

	<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 07:03:14 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:14Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>If fingerprinting is an issue with Tor than it is an issue with openssl.  Tor looks like openssl and a browser talking to a secure website.
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 9</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_9/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_9/</link>

	<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 07:03:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:15Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>How about developing a TOR button for &lt;b&gt;K-Meleon&lt;/b&gt;? It&#39;s an open source browser and it uses less system resources than Google Chrome.
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 10</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_10/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_10/</link>

	<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 07:03:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:16Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>hi~  when i use firefox-tor , i can&#39;t use the adobe plus,so i can&#39;t browse the youtube video ,i was so depressed about that ,can you tell me how can i copying with it, thank you!!
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 11</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_11/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Firefox_Private_Browsing_Mode_Torbutton_and_Fingerprinting/comment_11/</link>

	<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 07:03:17 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:03:17Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>hi~  when i use firefox-tor , i can&#39;t use the adobe plus,so i can&#39;t browse the youtube video ,i was so depressed about that ,can you tell me how can i copying with it, thank you!!
</description>


</item>

</channel>
</rss>
