<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>pages tagged research</title>
<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/research/"/>
<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/research/index.atom" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
<author>

<name>The Tor Blog</name>

</author>




<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/research/</id>

<subtitle type="html">The Tor Blog</subtitle>
<generator uri="http://ikiwiki.info/" version="3.20100722ubuntu1">ikiwiki</generator>
<updated>2011-04-05T12:15:45Z</updated>
<entry>
	<title>February 2011 Progress Report</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/February_2011_Progress_Report/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/February_2011_Progress_Report/"/>

	<author><name>phobos</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/bug_fixes" />

	<category term="/tags/censosrhip_circumvention" />

	<category term="/tags/downloads" />

	<category term="/tags/improvements" />

	<category term="/tags/incentives" />

	<category term="/tags/progress_report" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T12:15:45Z</updated>
	<published>2011-03-15T17:11:15Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New hires&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
We contracted Runa Sandvik to work on moving the torouter project forward, &lt;a href=&quot;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/wiki/TheOnionRouter/Torouter&quot; title=&quot;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/wiki/TheOnionRouter/Torouter&quot;&gt;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/wiki/TheOnionRouter/Torouter&lt;/a&gt;, translations, and integration of tor web server log analysis and publication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Releases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
On February 23rd, we released an updated Tor -stable.  Tor 0.2.1.30 fixes a&lt;br /&gt;
variety of less critical bugs. The main other change is a slight tweak to Tor&#39;s TLS handshake that makes relays and bridges that run this new version reachable from Iran again. We don&#39;t expect this tweak will win the arms race long-term, but it&lt;br /&gt;
buys us time until we roll out a better solution.  Full announcement at&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://lists.torproject.org/pipermail/tor-announce/2011-February/000000.html&quot; title=&quot;https://lists.torproject.org/pipermail/tor-announce/2011-February/000000.html&quot;&gt;https://lists.torproject.org/pipermail/tor-announce/2011-February/000000...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Censorship resistance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arm development has stayed relatively on track, with the revised&lt;br /&gt;
connection panel very nearly achieving parity with its predecessor&lt;br /&gt;
(and in most respects surpassing it). Most of what remains are&lt;br /&gt;
refinements and tasty new features. Arm has also been added to Debian&lt;br /&gt;
(Sid) and Ubuntu (Natty) with backports pending. Many thanks to Peter&lt;br /&gt;
for his help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Tom spent some time assisting Jacob with a satellite test.  The test wound&lt;br /&gt;
up breaking due to flaky hardware, however they were able to collect some usable&lt;br /&gt;
data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created the trac ticket around hidden service improvements,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/ticket/2552&quot; title=&quot;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/ticket/2552&quot;&gt;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/ticket/2552&lt;/a&gt;. We need to focus on&lt;br /&gt;
improving hidden services and fixing some of the performance and reliability&lt;br /&gt;
issues within.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mike fixed a bunch of torbutton bugs.  His summary iteration results are&lt;br /&gt;
at &lt;a href=&quot;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/ticket/2591&quot; title=&quot;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/ticket/2591&quot;&gt;https://trac.torproject.org/projects/tor/ticket/2591&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mike helped fix the bandwidth authority on salsa that exploded due to a&lt;br /&gt;
reinstall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture and Design Docs for better censorship resistance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karsten and Sebastian tried to improve the database schema in metrics-db&lt;br /&gt;
to speed up relay search performance.  Unfortunately, the required updates&lt;br /&gt;
from the old schema took forever, so we don&#39;t just need a better schema, but&lt;br /&gt;
also a better migration strategy to go from one schema to the next. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karsten started moving code from metrics-db to metrics-web to make the&lt;br /&gt;
metrics website a self-contained unit that&#39;s independent of&lt;br /&gt;
aggregating descriptors.  The idea is that people can take the metrics-web&lt;br /&gt;
code and improve it or replace it with a better metrics website written in&lt;br /&gt;
the web language of their choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karsten started working on better visualizations of Tor data using the&lt;br /&gt;
Thematic Mapping API together with Rachel Binx. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hide Tor&#39;s network signature.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborated with George K on obfsproxy, a generic protocol&lt;br /&gt;
obfuscator.  It seems to work ok but needs more testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nick worked on improving the pluggable-transport design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob did another revision on what is now prop 179,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitweb.torproject.org/torspec.git/blob/HEAD:/proposals/179-TLS-cert-and-parameter-normalization.txt&quot; title=&quot;https://gitweb.torproject.org/torspec.git/blob/HEAD:/proposals/179-TLS-cert-and-parameter-normalization.txt&quot;&gt;https://gitweb.torproject.org/torspec.git/blob/HEAD:/proposals/179-TLS-c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob looked at the EFF SSL data and have some improvements for how we can&lt;br /&gt;
get better data for future research questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outreach and Advocacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob continued working on Egypt related issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob did a training for people in Bahrain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tor, the ACLU and the OPC launched our privacy challenge:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.develop4privacy.org/&quot; title=&quot;http://www.develop4privacy.org/&quot;&gt;http://www.develop4privacy.org/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob did a bit of looking at the Libyan Internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob gave the keynote speech at the Ctrl-X-Ethics Workshop in Toronto on&lt;br /&gt;
ethics of security research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We ran a successful hackfest with the help of MITs Center for Future Civic&lt;br /&gt;
Media, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/tor-open-hackfest-february-19-2011&quot; title=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/tor-open-hackfest-february-19-2011&quot;&gt;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/tor-open-hackfest-february-19-2011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
and the followup at &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/hackfest-thanks&quot; title=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/hackfest-thanks&quot;&gt;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/hackfest-thanks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roger was the keynote speaker for Workshop on Free and Open Communication&lt;br /&gt;
on the Internet (FOCI), &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gtisc.gatech.edu/foci.html&quot; title=&quot;http://www.gtisc.gatech.edu/foci.html&quot;&gt;http://www.gtisc.gatech.edu/foci.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrew talked to the Wesleyan HFOSS team about Tor and classwork for their&lt;br /&gt;
Summer 2011 session. &lt;a href=&quot;http://hfoss.org/&quot; title=&quot;http://hfoss.org/&quot;&gt;http://hfoss.org/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roger and Steven presented at Financial Crypto and the Workshop on the&lt;br /&gt;
Ethics of Computer Security Research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrew spoke at a few panels under Chatham House Rules.  He published his&lt;br /&gt;
speech notes as a blog post,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/five-minutes-speak&quot; title=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/five-minutes-speak&quot;&gt;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/five-minutes-speak&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roger wrote a blog post about using our data archive as input to new&lt;br /&gt;
safety metrics:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/research-problem-measuring-safety-tor-&quot; title=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/research-problem-measuring-safety-tor-&quot;&gt;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/research-problem-measuring-safety-tor-&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roger talked to the Philly FBI for the Philadelphia Infragard chapter&lt;br /&gt;
about Tor and anonymity online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roger taught a Tor lecture for Drexel&#39;s security class.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrew was interviewed by Discovery News about Tor&#39;s role in the unrest in&lt;br /&gt;
Tunisia and Egypt,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://news.discovery.com/tech/egypt-internet-online-protesters-110201.html&quot; title=&quot;http://news.discovery.com/tech/egypt-internet-online-protesters-110201.html&quot;&gt;http://news.discovery.com/tech/egypt-internet-online-protesters-110201.h...&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrew was interviewed by the Walpole Times about Tor and what we do,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wickedlocal.com/walpole/news/x95296113/Tor-Project-a-Walpole-&quot; title=&quot;http://www.wickedlocal.com/walpole/news/x95296113/Tor-Project-a-Walpole-&quot;&gt;http://www.wickedlocal.com/walpole/news/x95296113/Tor-Project-a-Walpole-&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
based-company-helps-Egyptians-avoid-Internet-censorship-during-protests. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preconfigured privacy bundles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob did some testing of Gibberbot&#39;s Tor and OTR integration. Gibberbot&lt;br /&gt;
is an XMPP chat client for Android designed to work over Tor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob did a bunch of work on ttdnsd - some important (but not critical)&lt;br /&gt;
bug fixes and he&#39;s planning on pushing out a release in the future. Jacob and&lt;br /&gt;
Robert did some work on torsocks integration and in the process hammered out a&lt;br /&gt;
reasonable torsocks API for people who want to have auto-magically Torified&lt;br /&gt;
sockets without understanding Tor internals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob worked on OpenWRT packaging issues - as well as other work on the&lt;br /&gt;
Torouter project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob worked on Tahoe (&lt;a href=&quot;http://tahoe-lafs.org/trac/tahoe-lafs&quot; title=&quot;http://tahoe-lafs.org/trac/tahoe-lafs&quot;&gt;http://tahoe-lafs.org/trac/tahoe-lafs&lt;/a&gt;) and&lt;br /&gt;
Tor related Hidden Service documentation; after moderate amount of Tor testing&lt;br /&gt;
with Tahoe now and it seems to be partially functional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bridge work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karsten prepared a patch for BridgeDB to export bridge pool assignments to&lt;br /&gt;
a local file.  This patch needs some cleanup before being deployed on&lt;br /&gt;
BridgeDB.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karsten wrote a first draft of a BridgeDB specification that Nick&lt;br /&gt;
commented on. The next step is to include Nick&#39;s comments and change the&lt;br /&gt;
writing style, so that the specification describes what the current BridgeDB&lt;br /&gt;
code does, not what a generic BridgeDB implemention should do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karsten extended the bridge descriptor sanitizing algorithm to include IP&lt;br /&gt;
   address hashes in the sanitized descriptors.  Sanitized all existing&lt;br /&gt;
   bridge descriptors using this new algorithm.  Instead of 127.0.0.1,&lt;br /&gt;
   bridges now have 10.x.y.z addresses with x.y.z being stable for a given&lt;br /&gt;
   bridge fingerprint in a given month.  This allows analyses of how often&lt;br /&gt;
   bridges change their IP addresses in a given month.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian deployed a new version of BridgeDB, the one that&#39;s i18n enabled&lt;br /&gt;
(#1613) and also can dump bridge pool assignments to files. We can now&lt;br /&gt;
assign an amount of unassigned bridges to someone/something and dump&lt;br /&gt;
them to file buckets. See #1612 for more infos. In theory, we can now&lt;br /&gt;
have an amount of Twitter assigned bridges that we pump out over&lt;br /&gt;
Twitter. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian also started writing a python script that is able to dump&lt;br /&gt;
stuff to Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After deployment of the new BridgeDB, some issues came up that were fixed&lt;br /&gt;
(#2556 and others). It seems to run smoothly now. We&#39;ll be even more&lt;br /&gt;
happy about it when we have important (read: Chinese and Farsi)&lt;br /&gt;
translations ready and deployed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian and Karsten discussed about whether his planned &quot;dump bridge&lt;br /&gt;
pool&lt;br /&gt;
assignments to files&quot; feature can use the bucket mechanism of #1612.&lt;br /&gt;
Turns out it can&#39;t since both have a different set of goals and would&lt;br /&gt;
be to painful to sync with every change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mike helped Karsten with improving the output of Torperf for future&lt;br /&gt;
experiments involving circuit build timeouts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scalability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved Torperf and finally deployed it to collect data about used&lt;br /&gt;
   paths and to measure performance with custom guard node selections.&lt;br /&gt;
   This is still work in progress together with Mike and Tom as part of&lt;br /&gt;
   our first Scrum iteration that ends on March 5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked on Florian&#39;s and Björn&#39;s token bucket patch some more together&lt;br /&gt;
   with Sebastian.  The current state of the patch is that it needs some&lt;br /&gt;
   more love before it can be merged into 0.2.3.x.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nick collaborated a little with two volunteers on what we&lt;br /&gt;
think at this point must be the 5th generation of a &quot;launch a private&lt;br /&gt;
network&quot; tool.  This one is called &quot;chutney&quot;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nick reviewed a bunch of patches, reviewed a bunch of bugs, fixed a&lt;br /&gt;
bunch of bugs, merged many people&#39;s code, got 0.2.2.x closer to done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sebastian wrote a proposal for a safer voting process for consensus&lt;br /&gt;
parameters, and wrote an implementation for it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitweb.torproject.org/torspec.git/blob/HEAD:/proposals/178-param-&quot; title=&quot;https://gitweb.torproject.org/torspec.git/blob/HEAD:/proposals/178-param-&quot;&gt;https://gitweb.torproject.org/torspec.git/blob/HEAD:/proposals/178-param...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
voting.txt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Damian started thinking about our various projects in a more streamlined&lt;br /&gt;
and easy-to-understand way.  The results are at&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/getinvolved/volunteer.html.en#Projects&quot; title=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/getinvolved/volunteer.html.en#Projects&quot;&gt;https://www.torproject.org/getinvolved/volunteer.html.en#Projects&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incentives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian cleaned up the rather hackish installation of Weather on bahri.&lt;br /&gt;
The stable installation now lives under `/home/weather/opt/current&#39; and actually&lt;br /&gt;
is update-able through `git pull&#39;. There&#39;s also a testing installation to test&lt;br /&gt;
stuff and play around at &lt;a href=&quot;https://weather2.torproject.org/&quot; title=&quot;https://weather2.torproject.org/&quot;&gt;https://weather2.torproject.org/&lt;/a&gt;. He&#39;s tried to&lt;br /&gt;
update the documentation with all the stuff that is necessary to install and run&lt;br /&gt;
Weather.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian tried looking into #2467. Some people complained that Weather&lt;br /&gt;
didn&#39;t know their relay fingerprint. On Sebastian&#39;s and Mike&#39;s idea, Christian&lt;br /&gt;
changed the torrc to include `FetchDirInfoEarly 1&#39; and `FetchUselessDescriptors&lt;br /&gt;
1&#39;. Since that no one complained again about Weather not knowing a certain relay&lt;br /&gt;
(except for one time, when the Weather process had silently crashed and&lt;br /&gt;
therefore the database wasn&#39;t updated for a day). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After Tor 0.2.1.30 was tagged and made it to the recommended versions&#39;,&lt;br /&gt;
people running 0.2.1.29 started complaining about getting &quot;Node out of date!&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
emails from Weather. It turned out that Weather was actually doing the right&lt;br /&gt;
thing, namely mailing them that they were not running the latest recommended&lt;br /&gt;
stable version anymore. No one seemed to have read the text near the checkbox in&lt;br /&gt;
the signup process. After discussing this intensely with Sebastian, we decided&lt;br /&gt;
to go for a more simple solution: People now get email when they don&#39;t run one&lt;br /&gt;
of the recommended versions or a more recent dev version of Tor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More reliable downloads&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian did a rather large GetTor overhaul. The way GetTor manages its&lt;br /&gt;
packages is now much easier to understand and enhance. GetTor moved from a&lt;br /&gt;
ini-style configuration file and parser to a more BridgeDB-like configuration&lt;br /&gt;
management.  Also, packages are now configured rather than hard coded. In&lt;br /&gt;
addition, he cleaned up the i18n management of GetTor to something similar to&lt;br /&gt;
what we use in BridgeDB. Not only are the translation strings cleaner now, but&lt;br /&gt;
the translation and installation is smoother. Also, the logging was simplified&lt;br /&gt;
because it had too many features that no one used and generally was polluting&lt;br /&gt;
the log file with too much useless information. Furthermore, the MakeStat.py&lt;br /&gt;
script that&lt;br /&gt;
creates GetTor&#39;s package statistics was simplified a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian fixed #1586, users requesting non-existent split packages now&lt;br /&gt;
are informed about that fact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nick worked on a thandy packaging spec with Erinn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Translations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sebastian Started figuring out a way how translations can be pulled from&lt;br /&gt;
transifex and used in their respective products in a more automated&lt;br /&gt;
fashion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New or updated website translations in French, Russian, Italian, Japanese,&lt;br /&gt;
Spanish, Mandarin Chinese, and Greek.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/February_2011_Progress_Report/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/February_2011_Progress_Report/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Research problem: measuring the safety of the Tor network</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_measuring_the_safety_of_the_Tor_network/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_measuring_the_safety_of_the_Tor_network/"/>

	<author><name>arma</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/research" />

	<category term="/tags/research_progress" />

	<category term="/tags/thesis_idea" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T12:14:33Z</updated>
	<published>2011-02-06T05:18:00Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;We need a better understanding of how much anonymity the Tor network provides against a partial network adversary who observes and/or operates some of the network. Specifically, we want to understand the chances that this class of adversary can observe a user&#39;s traffic coming into the network and also the corresponding traffic exiting the network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of our graphs historically have looked at the total number of relays over time. But this simple scalar doesn&#39;t take into account relay capacity, exit policies, geographic or network location, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One concrete problem from this bad metric is that when many new relays show up (e.g. due to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/files/relays-diff-2011-01-28.png&quot;&gt;political event&lt;/a&gt;), we really don&#39;t have any insight about how the diversity of the new relays compares to the rest of the network. The simplistic metric also gets misused in academic research papers to produce misleading results like &quot;I can sign up 2% of the Tor relays and capture 50% of the paths,&quot; when what they mean is &quot;I can provide half the capacity in the Tor network and capture half the paths.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are four parts to this research problem. First, we need a broad array of metrics that reflect various instances of our partial network adversary. Second, we need to understand for each metric how stable it is (sensitivity analysis) and what changes in the Tor network would efficiently improve (or harm) it. Third, we should make the calculations as realistic as possible based on actual Tor client behavior. Last, we need a better infrastructure for comparing the safety impact from alternate design scenarios, for example different path selection or route balancing algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&#39;d love to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/research&quot;&gt;work with you&lt;/a&gt; to help answer these questions. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/research-problem-measuring-safety-tor-network&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_measuring_the_safety_of_the_Tor_network/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_measuring_the_safety_of_the_Tor_network/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Research problem: adaptive throttling of Tor clients by entry guards</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_adaptive_throttling_of_Tor_clients_by_entry_guards/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_adaptive_throttling_of_Tor_clients_by_entry_guards/"/>

	<author><name>arma</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/bandwidth_throttling" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />

	<category term="/tags/research_progress" />

	<category term="/tags/thesis_idea" />

	<category term="/tags/torperf" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T12:08:01Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-19T22:02:14Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;Looking for a paper topic (or a thesis topic)? Here&#39;s a Tor research area that needs more attention. The short version is: if we prevent the really loud users from using too much of the Tor network, how much can it help?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve instrumented Tor&#39;s entry relays so they can rate-limit connections from users, and we&#39;ve instrumented the directory authorities so they can change the rate-limiting parameters globally across the network. Which parameter values improve performance for the Tor network as a whole? How should relays adapt their rate-limiting parameters based on their capacity and based on the network load they see, and what rate-limiting algorithms will work best?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&#39;d love to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/research&quot;&gt;work with you&lt;/a&gt; to help answer these questions. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/research-problem-adaptive-throttling-tor-clients-entry-guards&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_adaptive_throttling_of_Tor_clients_by_entry_guards/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Research_problem_adaptive_throttling_of_Tor_clients_by_entry_guards/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>July 2010 Progress Report</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/July_2010_Progress_Report/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/July_2010_Progress_Report/"/>

	<author><name>phobos</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/alpha_releases" />

	<category term="/tags/bug_fixes" />

	<category term="/tags/development" />

	<category term="/tags/enhancements" />

	<category term="/tags/orbot" />

	<category term="/tags/performance_improvements" />

	<category term="/tags/portable_bundles" />

	<category term="/tags/progress_report" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />

	<category term="/tags/research_progress" />

	<category term="/tags/research_reports" />

	<category term="/tags/research_results" />

	<category term="/tags/tor_browser_bundle" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T12:06:28Z</updated>
	<published>2010-08-12T14:25:08Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New releases&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/july-2010-progress-report&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On July 4th, we released Tor Browser Bundle 1.3.7 for Microsoft Windows. This is a security update for Firefox and Pidgin. The changes are: update to Firefox 3.5.10 and Pidgin Instant Messenger 2.7.1r2 to fix some security issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On July 6th, we released Tor Browser Bundle 1.0.8 for GNU/Linux distributions. This fixes a number of security issues with included software. The updates include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update libpng to 1.4.3 (see CVE-2010-1205)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update Firefox to 3.5.10&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update HTTPS Everywhere to 0.2.1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/July_2010_Progress_Report/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/July_2010_Progress_Report/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>On the risks of serving whenever you surf</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/On_the_risks_of_serving_whenever_you_surf/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/On_the_risks_of_serving_whenever_you_surf/"/>

	<author><name>sjmurdoch</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/anonymity" />

	<category term="/tags/bridges" />

	<category term="/tags/censorship_circumvention" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T11:45:05Z</updated>
	<published>2009-12-23T22:27:12Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/bridges&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Bridge nodes&lt;/a&gt; are one of Tor&#39;s key architectural components for allowing wide access to the network. These act like normal Tor nodes, except there is no centralized list available to download, so it&#39;s harder to block access to all of them. Users who cannot access the Tor network in the normal way can find the IP addresses of a few bridges, and connect to the rest of the Tor network via these nodes. The bridge node IP addresses are distributed in a way such that anyone should be able to find a few, but it should be difficult for someone to find (and block access to) them all. Currently they are available by email or the web, but more strategies are being considered, such as instant messaging or MMORPGs. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/risks-serving-whenever-you-surf&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/On_the_risks_of_serving_whenever_you_surf/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/On_the_risks_of_serving_whenever_you_surf/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>TorFlow Node Capacity, Integrity and Reliability Measurements at HotPETS</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/TorFlow_Node_Capacity_Integrity_and_Reliability_Measurements_at_HotPETS/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/TorFlow_Node_Capacity_Integrity_and_Reliability_Measurements_at_HotPETS/"/>

	<author><name>mikeperry</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/performance" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T11:28:17Z</updated>
	<published>2009-06-21T09:32:49Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/measuring-tor-network-public-directory-information&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Like Karsten&lt;/a&gt;, I too am presenting at &lt;a href=&quot;http://petsymposium.org/2009/hotpets.php&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;HotPETS&lt;/a&gt; in Seattle in August. My presentation will cover my work with my &lt;a href=&quot;https://svn.torproject.org/svn/torflow/trunk/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;TorFlow suite&lt;/a&gt; - a python library and utility set to assist measuring and adjusting performance on the Tor network, and to scan the network for malfunctioning and misbehaving exits. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/torflow-node-capacity-integrity-and-reliability-measurements-hotpets&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/TorFlow_Node_Capacity_Integrity_and_Reliability_Measurements_at_HotPETS/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/TorFlow_Node_Capacity_Integrity_and_Reliability_Measurements_at_HotPETS/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Measuring the Tor Network from Public Directory Information</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Measuring_the_Tor_Network_from_Public_Directory_Information/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Measuring_the_Tor_Network_from_Public_Directory_Information/"/>

	<author><name>karsten</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/censorship_circumvention" />

	<category term="/tags/performance" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T11:27:12Z</updated>
	<published>2009-06-16T18:25:31Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;On this year&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://petsymposium.org/2009/hotpets.php&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;HotPETs workshop&lt;/a&gt; (August 5-7 in Seattle, WA, USA) I&#39;m going to present some results on &lt;a href=&quot;http://freehaven.net/~karsten/metrics/measuring-tor-public-dir-info-final.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Measuring the Tor Network from Public Directory Information&lt;/a&gt;. The main idea is to observe trends in the Tor network without having to measure any data other than &lt;a href=&quot;https://git.torproject.org/checkout/tor/master/doc/spec/dir-spec.txt&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;public directory information&lt;/a&gt;. These data are there anyway as they are required for clients to make good path selection decisions and build circuits. The results of this paper reveal problems in the current Tor network that need to be addressed, e.g., by &lt;a href=&quot;https://git.torproject.org/checkout/metrics/master/report/dirarch/flagrequirements-2009-04-11.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;lowering requirements for assigning certain flags&lt;/a&gt;, facilitating the upgrade process, improving support for dynamic IP addresses, possibly calculating bandwidth capacity more reliably, and clarifying legal issues for running relays in view of data retention laws. The next step in understanding the problems of the Tor network requires an &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/performance-measurements-and-blockingresistance-analysis-tor-network&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;extension of network measurements&lt;/a&gt; to improve &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/why-tor-is-slow&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;performance&lt;/a&gt; and blocking-resistance of Tor.&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Measuring_the_Tor_Network_from_Public_Directory_Information/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Measuring_the_Tor_Network_from_Public_Directory_Information/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Performance measurements and blocking-resistance analysis in the Tor network</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Performance_measurements_and_blocking-resistance_analysis_in_the_Tor_network/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Performance_measurements_and_blocking-resistance_analysis_in_the_Tor_network/"/>

	<author><name>karsten</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/censorship_circumvention" />

	<category term="/tags/performance" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T11:25:02Z</updated>
	<published>2009-05-21T20:19:22Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;The Tor network has grown to more than one thousand relays and millions of casual users over the past few years. We are proud of our network&#39;s popularity, but with growth has come increasing &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/why-tor-is-slow&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;performance problems&lt;/a&gt; and attempts by some countries to block access to the Tor network. In order to address these problems, we need to learn more about the Tor network. In this post, I describe the current state of network measurements in Tor and some proposed additions to help us understand the network better. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/performance-measurements-and-blockingresistance-analysis-tor-network&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Performance_measurements_and_blocking-resistance_analysis_in_the_Tor_network/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Performance_measurements_and_blocking-resistance_analysis_in_the_Tor_network/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>&#x22;&#x22;One</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/-One_cell_is_enough_to_break_Tors_anonymity-/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/-One_cell_is_enough_to_break_Tors_anonymity-/"/>

	<author><name>arma</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/attacks" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />

	<category term="/tags/tagging" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T11:19:41Z</updated>
	<published>2009-02-19T06:51:21Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow there&#39;s a talk at Black Hat DC by Xinwen Fu on an active attack that can allow traffic confirmation in Tor. He calls it a &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cs.uml.edu/~xinwenfu/paper/ICC08_Fu.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;replay attack&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, whereas we called it a &quot;tagging attack&quot; in the original Tor paper, but let&#39;s look at how it actually works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, remember the basics of how Tor provides anonymity. Tor clients &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/images/htw2.png&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;route their traffic&lt;/a&gt; over several (&lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.torproject.org/noreply/TheOnionRouter/TorFAQ#VariablePathLength&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;usually three&lt;/a&gt;) relays, with the goal that no single relay gets to learn both where the user is (call her Alice) and what site she&#39;s reaching (call it Bob).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tor design &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/svn/trunk/doc/design-paper/tor-design.html#subsec:threat-model&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;doesn&#39;t try to protect&lt;/a&gt; against an attacker who can see or measure both traffic going into the Tor network and also traffic coming out of the Tor network. That&#39;s because if you can see both flows, some &lt;a href=&quot;http://freehaven.net/anonbib/#danezis:pet2004&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;simple statistics&lt;/a&gt; let you decide whether they match up. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/one-cell-enough&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/-One_cell_is_enough_to_break_Tors_anonymity-/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/-One_cell_is_enough_to_break_Tors_anonymity-/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Overhead from directory info: past, present, future</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Overhead_from_directory_info_past_present_future/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Overhead_from_directory_info_past_present_future/"/>

	<author><name>arma</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/directory" />

	<category term="/tags/performance" />

	<category term="/tags/research" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T11:19:15Z</updated>
	<published>2009-02-16T07:05:16Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;A growing number of people want to use Tor in low-bandwidth contexts (e.g. modems or shared Internet cafes in the Middle East) and mobile contexts (start up a Tor client, use it for a short time, and then stop it again). Currently Tor is nearly unusable in these situations, because it spends too many bytes fetching directory info. This post summarizes the steps we&#39;ve taken so far to reduce directory overhead, and explains the steps that are coming next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, what do I mean by &quot;directory info&quot;? Part of the Tor design is the _discovery_ component: how clients learn about the available Tor relays, along with their keys, locations, exit policies, and so on. Tor&#39;s solution so far uses a few trusted directory authorities that sign and distribute official lists of the relays that make up the Tor network. &lt;span class=&quot;read-more&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.torproject.org/blog/overhead-directory-info%3A-past%2C-present%2C-future&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;read&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Overhead_from_directory_info_past_present_future/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Overhead_from_directory_info_past_present_future/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>

</feed>
