<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>pages tagged peer_to_peer</title>
<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/peer_to_peer/"/>
<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/peer_to_peer/index.atom" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
<author>

<name>The Tor Blog</name>

</author>




<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/peer_to_peer/</id>

<subtitle type="html">The Tor Blog</subtitle>
<generator uri="http://ikiwiki.info/" version="3.20100722ubuntu1">ikiwiki</generator>
<updated>2011-04-05T12:15:03Z</updated>
<entry>
	<title>five minutes to speak</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/five_minutes_to_speak/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/five_minutes_to_speak/"/>

	<author><name>phobos</name></author>






	<category term="/tags/censorship_circumvention" />

	<category term="/tags/cyberutopian" />

	<category term="/tags/peer_to_peer" />

	<category term="/tags/policy" />

	<category term="/tags/policy_makers" />

	<category term="/tags/technology" />


	<updated>2011-04-05T12:15:03Z</updated>
	<published>2011-02-13T14:52:43Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;I was asked to give a five minute speech to open a panel in front of a number of policy makers and advisors in Washington, DC in the past few weeks.  The discussion was under &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/wiki/Chatham_House_Rule&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Chatham House Rule&lt;/a&gt;.  A number of people have encouraged me to publish the speech notes as a blog post, it is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here I am, a technologist in a room full of policy people.  I&#39;ll stick&lt;br /&gt;
to what I know and try not to put anyone to sleep in the next five&lt;br /&gt;
minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technology is agnostic, who uses and how they use it matters.  Roads,&lt;br /&gt;
cars, phones, email, websites are all technologies used for good and bad.&lt;br /&gt;
In the 1930s, the feds and police warned of mass chaos if the interstate&lt;br /&gt;
highway system was built in the US.  The ability for criminals to quickly&lt;br /&gt;
transit between cities was of grave concern. Crime would spread faster,&lt;br /&gt;
further, and this would hasten the breakdown of the very fabric of the&lt;br /&gt;
American society, community. Time has shown the benefits vastly outweighed&lt;br /&gt;
the costs.  This same principle has shown to be true of the internet&lt;br /&gt;
and computer technology.  Sure, we may have new kinds of crime with botnets,&lt;br /&gt;
zombies, phishing, but do we really?  Lying, impersonation, and tricking&lt;br /&gt;
someone into doing your work are the same crimes they have been for the&lt;br /&gt;
past few millenia.  It&#39;s just that the substrate that is used, has changed.&lt;br /&gt;
What are some of the largest companies in the world?  GE, IBM, Apple,&lt;br /&gt;
Microsoft, Google.  What one should or should not do is policy and law,&lt;br /&gt;
what one can actually do or not do is technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Circumvention, anonymity, and privacy tools used in a free world can be&lt;br /&gt;
a minor annoyance, i.e. wikileaks used wikis, ssl, email, and yes, tor,&lt;br /&gt;
but in the end, it&#39;s an annoyance.  We don&#39;t have people in the streets&lt;br /&gt;
rioting trying to overthrow our govt. Wikipedia uses the same technology&lt;br /&gt;
in wikis, ssl, and email. Everyone loves Wikipedia and considers it a net positive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The same circumvention, anonymity, and privacy tools are deadly to&lt;br /&gt;
repressive regimes.  The free flow of information and education are of&lt;br /&gt;
great concern to a regime trying to control the horizontal and vertical&lt;br /&gt;
of every day life. The tactics a regime can use are legal, technical,&lt;br /&gt;
and physical.  The regime can switch between tactics, generally&lt;br /&gt;
depending upon what&#39;s economical and most effective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roughly 1 billion people are online in some way.  Berkman did a study&lt;br /&gt;
that found roughly 2% of that billion know what a proxy is, or even that&lt;br /&gt;
technology exists to circumvent internet censorship.  98% of the world&lt;br /&gt;
accepts that facebook, google, cnn, and the bbc, are blocked and doesn&#39;t&lt;br /&gt;
try to find ways around it. This doesn&#39;t even broach the topic of online&lt;br /&gt;
privacy relating to commercial entities nor law enforcement and&lt;br /&gt;
intelligence agencies trying to learn the who, what, where, and how of your Internet activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arguing about which proxy technology should get all of the funding and&lt;br /&gt;
attention is silly.  The budgets and adversaries vastly outweigh the&lt;br /&gt;
funding and research into proxies.  It&#39;s not a zero-sum game, and&lt;br /&gt;
the different technologies take very different approaches to success;&lt;br /&gt;
freegate/ultrasurf, vpns, psiphon, and web proxies play a game of cat&lt;br /&gt;
and mouse with ip addresses and sometimes encryption; tor uses the&lt;br /&gt;
strategy of R&amp;amp;D and protecting ones anonymity and privacy first, the&lt;br /&gt;
secondary effects of this are well-suited to circumvention too.  Tor,&lt;br /&gt;
freegate, psiphon, and vpns sum up to roughly $50m in funding from the US govt&lt;br /&gt;
of the past few years.  Only a very small fraction of that total has made it to actual technology.  Compare that to the billions spent on snakeoil&lt;br /&gt;
black box technology by the DoD and intelligence agencies preparing for&lt;br /&gt;
a cyberwar arms race, much like the nuclear arms race, to deter other&lt;br /&gt;
nations from attacking us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I talked to a member of a terrorist organization in Vietnam.  He&#39;s been&lt;br /&gt;
stalked, harassed, and had everything confiscated multiple times by his&lt;br /&gt;
government.  You know his organization as Deutsche Welle.  He&#39;s a&lt;br /&gt;
reporter.  He had no idea how his plans, documents, and contacts were&lt;br /&gt;
being discovered and used against him. His ability to understand the&lt;br /&gt;
differences between Tor, JAP, and Freegate was like asking which tires&lt;br /&gt;
are best for gravel, snow, or tarmac.  The question he didn&#39;t even know&lt;br /&gt;
to ask is, &quot;What are safe and secure computing and online practices?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;
to use my analogy, &quot;what car do I want for those tires?  the answer is&lt;br /&gt;
a rally car.&quot;   I spent 4 hours going over how the internet works,&lt;br /&gt;
how to think about adversaries online, what is ssl, what it means, what&lt;br /&gt;
are phishing, viruses, botnets, and state-sponsored malware.  By the&lt;br /&gt;
end of the 4th hour, he understood how tor is different than a simple&lt;br /&gt;
vpn or proxy server, and when to use tor and when it isn&#39;t needed. 3.5h&lt;br /&gt;
of that discussion was basic operational, computer, and online security&lt;br /&gt;
and safe practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So where does this leave us?  It leaves us with a mix of education,&lt;br /&gt;
technology, and many, many unanswered questions.  This is a young field&lt;br /&gt;
overall.  As the censorship providers and technologies get better, so&lt;br /&gt;
will those circumvention technologies.  Educating users about internet&lt;br /&gt;
safety, risks, and making the tools vastly easier and safer to use&lt;br /&gt;
should be a goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tor published a &quot;10 things to think about circumvention tools&quot; paper to&lt;br /&gt;
try to distill what we&#39;ve learned over the past 10 years of doing this.&lt;br /&gt;
In a few of these areas, tor is not the best choice, for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What about technology?  Isn&#39;t it going to save us all?  Currently,&lt;br /&gt;
freegate/ultrasurf, vpns, and web proxies are looking for money to fund&lt;br /&gt;
their growing infrastructure costs. The more users you have, the more&lt;br /&gt;
servers, more bandwidth, and more costs you incur.  Its a quick way to&lt;br /&gt;
spend lots of money and get lots of users.  However becoming the ISP for&lt;br /&gt;
the world gets very expensive, very quickly as you scale up to hundreds&lt;br /&gt;
of millions of users.  Look at the infrastructures of google, facebook,&lt;br /&gt;
yahoo, and microsoft to see the challenges that lie ahead for these tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tor and &quot;distributed tools&quot; look to improve the research and development&lt;br /&gt;
and rely on the scaling of users to both provide the circumvention and&lt;br /&gt;
grow to become a self-sustaining ISP to the world.  We have only begun&lt;br /&gt;
to see the power and effects of these technologies with bittorrent, jap,&lt;br /&gt;
skype, freenet, i2p, and tor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

	</content>


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/five_minutes_to_speak/#comments" type="text/html" />


	<link rel="comments" href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/five_minutes_to_speak/comments.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />

</entry>

</feed>
