<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" >
<channel>
<title>June 2009 Progress Report</title>
<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/</link>
<description>The Tor Blog</description>
<item>

	<title>JustMe (not verified): Comment 1</title>
	<dcterms:creator>JustMe (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_1/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_1/</link>

	<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 06:30:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:30:13Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Less Progress, }-(.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having trouble getting tor to run.&lt;br /&gt;
Would be nice for a little more laymans if possible instructions.&lt;br /&gt;
Could the problem be with my current Anti Virus programs and how to deal with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Norton and Spyware Doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Herb&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>JUstMe (not verified): Comment 2</title>
	<dcterms:creator>JUstMe (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_2/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_2/</link>

	<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 06:30:14 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:30:14Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;When I say layman I mean somewhere there was a note about, Opening a port.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come on guys and gals some of us would like to set up a relay know a little about the tech stuff but not a lot? Thus the how to do for the layman?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Herb&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>phobos: Comment 3</title>
	<dcterms:creator>phobos</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_3/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_3/</link>

	<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 06:30:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:30:15Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>Use Vidalia, point and click and use the &quot;Automatic Port Configuration&quot; option, it will try to do everything for you.  See &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/docs/tor-doc-relay.html.en#setup&quot; title=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/docs/tor-doc-relay.html.en#setup&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://www.torproject.org/docs/tor-doc-relay.html.en#setup&lt;/a&gt;
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>rmac (not verified): Comment 4</title>
	<dcterms:creator>rmac (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_4/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/June_2009_Progress_Report/comment_4/</link>

	<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 06:30:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:30:16Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;First I would like to thank everyone who made these programs available to someone like me who doesn&#39;t have the necessary skills to do this on my own. I first came across the Tor Project when I was looking into the stories of North Korea and the recent DNS attacks. I wanted to know more about how true this was. From what I have read a high school student can do this on his home PC and it could look like it was an attack by a hostile government. Anyway, I was also concerned about the new NSA mega billion dollar listening operation the US is building. Not that I have any state secrets to hide, mostly I just want to keep my bank account and credit card info secure when I go online. So now I have Tor, Incognito and Back Track 3. I used Back Track 3 to monitor myself to see how much info I was leaking to who knows? While I am quite satisfied with using Incognito on my laptop for anything that has to be absolutely secure I did have some questions about being &quot;attacked&quot;. I wanted to know if there was a way for me to monitor surveillance of my PC. Is there something that would give an alert that an attempt was being made to scan my transmissions or PC? How would I know if someone was using a program like Back Track to capture my information? For example If I was in China, Iran, or Honduras and I was sending info that was being censored how would I know if the military or police was going to be knocking down my door? Hope this makes sense. Any references where I could do some research on this would be appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again thanks for TOR and Incognito&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;rmac&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>

</channel>
</rss>
