<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" >
<channel>
<title>pages tagged low_bandwidth_clients</title>
<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/tags/low_bandwidth_clients/</link>
<description>The Tor Blog</description>
<item>

	<title>phobos: Protecting your Internet traffic in volatile times</title>
	<dcterms:creator>phobos</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Protecting_your_Internet_traffic_in_volatile_times/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Protecting_your_Internet_traffic_in_volatile_times/</link>


	<category>/tags/egypt</category>

	<category>/tags/low_bandwidth_clients</category>

	<category>/tags/tor_camouflage</category>

	<category>/tags/tor_on_satellite</category>

	<category>/tags/volatile_internet</category>


	<pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 14:18:23 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T12:14:30Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re glad that the Internet Service Providers in Egypt are announcing their routes to the world and have &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.renesys.com/blog/2011/02/egypt-returns-to-the-internet.shtml&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;rejoined the Internet&lt;/a&gt;.  We are concerned because it is possible that traffic crossing the Egyptian border is being recorded and possibly saved for future use.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/download/download#warning&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Correctly using Tor&lt;/a&gt; to and from Egyptian destinations will keep your traffic anonymous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tor separates who you are from where you are going on the Internet.  It&#39;s up to you, the user, to choose where you share your personal information. Currently, we do not try very hard to hide that you are using Tor.  In the past few years, we haven&#39;t needed to hide. Tor looks like an SSL connection on the wire. Your local ISP, if they are very clever, could map your current connections from your assigned IP address to the list of public Tor relays. This would only tell them you are using Tor, not where you are going on the Internet. We do offer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/docs/bridges.html.en&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;bridge relays&lt;/a&gt;, which are semi-public relays published in a few selective ways. By using bridges, your ISP is unlikely to figure out you are using Tor. We need thousands more bridges, please &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/docs/tor-doc-relay&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;join the Tor network&lt;/a&gt; to help others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, we theorized this arms race could happen.  Recent events have turned theory into reality. We are working on improvements to make it much more difficult to detect Tor usage. These methods include &lt;a href=&quot;https://gitweb.torproject.org/tor.git/blob/HEAD:/doc/spec/proposals/176-revising-handshake.txt&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;normalization of our TLS usage&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://gitweb.torproject.org/tor.git/blob/HEAD:/doc/spec/proposals/ideas/xxx-pluggable-transport.txt&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;tunneling&lt;/a&gt; Tor through other protocols, such as XMPP, HTTPS, and HTTP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to some &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.avaaz.org/en/egypt_blackout/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;funding from Avaaz&lt;/a&gt;, we&#39;ve also begun experimenting with ways to make Tor perform better on satellite and mesh networks.  We have Tor working well on &lt;a href=&quot;https://guardianproject.info/apps/orbot/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;mobile phone 3G and 4G connections&lt;/a&gt;. Tor over &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/wiki/Very_small_aperture_terminal&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;VSAT&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/wiki/Broadband_Global_Area_Network&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;BGAN&lt;/a&gt; connections does work, however it needs more research into how to better handle the variable latencies and varying available bandwidth on such connections.  The improvements that result from this research will benefit those with little to no Internet access, whether due to political unrest, natural disasters, or remote locations, who nonetheless seek to keep their online activities safe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>


	<comments>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Protecting_your_Internet_traffic_in_volatile_times/#comments</comments>

</item>
<item>

	<title>phobos: The NLnet Foundation funds two projects</title>
	<dcterms:creator>phobos</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/The_NLnet_Foundation_funds_two_projects/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/The_NLnet_Foundation_funds_two_projects/</link>


	<category>/tags/directory_services</category>

	<category>/tags/funding</category>

	<category>/tags/hidden_services</category>

	<category>/tags/low_bandwidth_clients</category>

	<category>/tags/nlnet</category>

	<category>/tags/tor_protocol</category>


	<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 21:04:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:07:24Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re happy to announce the NLnet Foundation is funding two enhancements for the Tor software and network.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two projects are summarized below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.torproject.org/projects/lowbandwidth&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Tor for low-bandwidth clients&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;p&gt;The Tor anonymity system is currently only usable by internet users who have high-bandwith connections. Upon the start of the Tor client, a large file with all Tor server descriptions is being downloaded. An evolution of the Tor protocol is aimed to reduce the initial download size. The new Tor protocol version shall change the way a client receives the information for its Tor circuit setup in a way, that the initial download can be performed over a slow modem line in less then three minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.torproject.org/projects/hidserv&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Speeding up Hidden Services&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;p&gt;The Tor anonymity system contains an important function that is called Tor Hidden Services, which allows users to set up anonymous information services, like websites, that can only be accessed through the Tor network and are protected against identification of the host that runs the services. Using these function, critical political and human rights information can be published in a way that protects the publisher and users of the service from repression and identification. The most critical limitation of this function is the time it takes until a Hidden Service is registered in the network and the latency of contact establishment when accessed by a user. The aim of this project is to develop the new protocol which will change the way Tor circuits are set up between the user and the Hidden Service as well as the way a Hidden Service is registered in the Tor network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>


	<comments>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/The_NLnet_Foundation_funds_two_projects/#comments</comments>

</item>

</channel>
</rss>
