<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" >
<channel>
<title>October 2009 Progress Report</title>
<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/October_2009_Progress_Report/</link>
<description>The Tor Blog</description>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous (not verified): Comment 1</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/October_2009_Progress_Report/comment_1/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/October_2009_Progress_Report/comment_1/</link>

	<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 06:41:01 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:41:01Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;&quot;Andrew gave a talk about Freedom of Speech, Online Censorship, and Tor at the US Agency for International Development. It was attended by members of US AID, State Department, and National Security Staff from The White House.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am both scared and impressed at the people you attract to your talks.  I will go with impressive, for the alternative is too scary to think about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you ever meet with other governments?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>phobos: Comment 2</title>
	<dcterms:creator>phobos</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/October_2009_Progress_Report/comment_2/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/October_2009_Progress_Report/comment_2/</link>

	<pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 06:41:02 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:41:02Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;We try to.  Generally, it makes more sense for someone motivated and a native speaker of the language to talk to the governments themselves.  We&#39;re willing to show up and provide support and do a talk, but many times English is the native language of the audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of these meetings are to educate them about Tor, internet censorship, and why blocking and filtering technologies don&#39;t stop the targetted audience and merely end up impacting normal law-abiding citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many times, at least in America, civil liberties and human rights get a lot of support from surprising places.  Having us talk about the reason we have a constitution is generally a fine way to gain support to stop a lot of draconian laws and policies from being adopted.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>

</channel>
</rss>
