<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>Ten Things to Look for in a Circumvention Tool</title>
<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/"/>
<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comments.atom" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
<author>

<name>phobos</name>

</author>




<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/</id>

<subtitle type="html">The Tor Blog</subtitle>
<generator uri="http://ikiwiki.info/" version="3.20100722ubuntu1">ikiwiki</generator>
<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:59Z</updated>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 1</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_1/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_1/"/>

	<author><name>Anonymous</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:53Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-17T12:07:53Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;Hi phobos!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, i never heard before of &quot;Roger Dingledine&quot;-&quot;leader for The Tor Project&quot;, but his article is very well written!!!!!!!!!!! It&#39;s a short (ten points, with introduction and conclusion) essay in nine pages!!!!!! Not much long ago, i thought about something like what he described in his article!!!!! YEAH, i thought about that and i found, say, the &quot;eleventh-thing to look in a Circumvention Tool&quot;!!!!!!!!!!!!! And, this thing is even funny!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! or at least, it&#39;s funny at the first appearance!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked myself: &quot;a Circumvention Tool&quot; ... &quot;11. Would criminals use it&quot; !!!??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, i think that to be the most mixed-up and unusual reason to use a software in general!!!!!, but i think i found a very good logic in it!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe the most powerful organizations/groups able to monitor and control the internet traffic are governments!!!!!! because, theoretically and technically, they can control all the ISPs and wiretap all the cables on the soil of their country!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, if criminals are breaking the law, and the police is not able to catch them!! then the software ought be considered fairly safe!!!!!!!!!! Would criminals using an unsafe software?!!! I think no!!!!!!!!!!!!! i think criminals are very often smart people: bad but also smart people (and this explains why they exist)!!!! So, as long as well-aged criminals are using a specified Circumvention Tool, this means that Tool being safe!!!!!!!!!!! So, you can also use it for your own purposes!!!!!!! If the `cops&#39; were unable to `bust&#39; the criminals, nobody will ever go after you!!!!!!!!!! not even evil multinational companies!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is funny even more if you think about another detail!!! Because, there is another super very strange thing!!!!!!! Why would you use a software like TOR?!!!! Well, for example, somewhere it&#39;s okay to use it just as a privacy tool, to deceive AdSense or Phorm-like tracking systems, and similar well known anti-privacy stalkers!!!!!!!!!!!!!! but sometimes it&#39;s also okay to use it to break the law!!!!!!!!!! Yeah, also the TorProject promotes this!!!! Because somewhere, it&#39;s only illegal to spread computer viruses (virii!!!), death threats, spam, hate mails, defamation posts, dangerous hoaxes, terrorists propaganda, doing privacy violations and so on!!!! and it&#39;s indeed good if those things are not allowed!! but somewhere it&#39;s also outlaw to criticize the government, politicians, abuses of military personnel and so!!!!!!!!!!!!! So, somehow or other, TOR is made with the main purpose to «break the law» and to «publish outlaw news», to break out of the juggernaut of censorship!!!!!!!! This is strange though!! If it&#39;s up to you to decide to which laws agree with, then there is no reason to have laws at all!!!!! but it&#39;s also widely known that anarchy is a broken off idea, and it&#39;ll never work!!!!! So, good Circumvention Tools require also good users!!!!!!!! because the quality of the TOR-NETWORK is made up after the quality of the people using it!!!!!!!!!!!!! YEAH!!!!!!!!! I think TOR is safe, or at least fairly safe, because nobody managed to broke anyone&#39;s anonymity!!!!! Insofar as i know, no one governmental agency ever managed to catch a TOR user doing something of illegal!!!!! Thereof, either: there is no criminal using TOR, or TOR is really safe!!!!!!! i think the second one!!! because, for sure, a lot of the illegal and very nasty things i listed before were also done through TOR!! no place is made of 100% trustworthy and good people!!! and this is also the reason why the whole idea of &quot;anarchism&quot; is a total failure!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, i think there is a lot of logic in what i wrote!!! but i also think there is something of potentially dangerous, baleful in the consequences of a very well working anonymity software like TOR when it&#39;s used by &quot;the real bad guys&quot;!!!!! also, because it&#39;s again recursively up to you to decide who are &quot;the real bad guys&quot;!!!! Muslim terrorists think the &quot;the real bad guys&quot; are all atheists, all westerners!!!!!!!!!!!! I don&#39;t know if you&#39;re also able to see the latent dark side of TOR!!!! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, okay, my conclusion about TOR is this one: «TOR is a old well-tested widely-known software and indeed TOR works!! for better or for worse, if a &quot;Circumvention Tool&quot; works for criminals, it&#39;ll work for all as well!!!!!!» &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bye!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
~bee!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;


	</content>



</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 2</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_2/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_2/"/>

	<author><name>Anonymous</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:54Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-20T12:07:54Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;First of all, I want you to stop and think about what anarchism on the Internet would look like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there ever was a proving ground for anarchy, it is here. Each individual (and group -- &#39;corporations&#39; too) has their own responsibility to secure their information and services, and provide what they will to who they will. There is no need for law here, only code. The only purpose law serves here is for vengeance. If someone wrongs you here because you fail to secure your information, have they done wrong? Yes, they have. However, using the law to prosecute them as opposed to changing your service, business model, and code is only seeking revenge, and is a waste of your energy that accomplishes nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your point about TOR as safe because it is being used by criminals is an interesting one, but ultimately untrue. Criminals actually have some pretty good resources at the moment. Many of which are better than TOR: http://bit.ly/axueYq&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These tools are not better because of technology, the actual technology is usually absolute shit (trust me, I have seen it). The reason why these tools are better is because they are obscure. Yes, criminals enjoy security through obscurity. There  are so many of them, and many times as many more poorly secured PCs. There is no hope at all of combating them through law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a government, all you really can do is capitalize on people&#39;s fears to create more laws to provide you with the surveillance tools to better monitor how your propaganda persuades the populace to give you more power. Especially in cases of war. Once you have dragnet surveillance to make you instantly aware of the results, propaganda now becomes a science that you can test, target, and repeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe this is why TOR is allowed to exist. Sure, dumb criminals use TOR because they can&#39;t figure out how to pay for something better. But mostly those criminals are just trolls and forum spammers. Real criminals don&#39;t use TOR because TOR IPs are obviously detected and if you are committing a crime, the LAST thing you want is someone looking extra closely at your actions because your source IP is in some DNSRBL. So you use that stolen credit card you have to buy some extra slices from a botnet of normal, innocent residential PCs before placing the order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, TOR software is good, and probably even the best. But never being suspected in the first place beats the best technology every time...&lt;/p&gt;


	</content>



</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 3</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_3/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_3/"/>

	<author><name>Anonymous</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:55Z</updated>
	<published>2010-10-04T12:07:55Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;Hi!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, if the technology of those &quot;underground&quot; tools is so very bad!!!!! i think &quot;dumb criminals&quot; (not so much dumb!!!!!) could use the TOR-NETWORK to chain it with their &quot;private proxies&quot; (&quot;botnets&quot;)!!!!!!!!! Yeah!!! in this way they can have both: Tor&#39;s security and being unsuspected!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, THANK YOU!!!!!!!!!!! because so far your post is the best and most interesting answer i ever got at the TOR&#39;s blog!!!!!!!!!!!!!! though i think, in some way or other, the TOR NETWORK could be very useful for criminals too!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bye!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;
~bee!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;


	</content>



</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 4</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_4/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_4/"/>

	<author><name>Anonymous</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:56Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-19T12:07:56Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;You never heard about Roger!?!  How about Nick Mathewson?  I know you heard about Mike Perry &lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/../../smileys/smile4.png&quot; alt=&quot;;-)&quot; /&gt;  I guess you can&#39;t take the time to learn about Tor as I&#39;m sure it takes all your time just typing all those dame exclamation points.  I thought you went away, and I was happy, now our back I&#39;m sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. how many keyboards do you go through a week, or maybe you just replace the exclamation point key which I&#39;m sure you wear out in a day.  &lt;/p&gt;


	</content>



</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 5</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_5/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_5/"/>

	<author><name>Anonymous</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:57Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-19T12:07:57Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	It&#39;s *NOT* &quot;TOR&quot; for crying out loud, it&#39;s &quot;Tor&quot;.  Get it right will you!?!

	</content>



</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 6</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_6/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_6/"/>

	<author><name>Anonymous</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:58Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-23T12:07:58Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;Why don&#39;t you guys just shut up and try a bit harder to make tor work again? Don&#39;t you see the sharp decreasing number of tor users? Tor &#39;s been not usable since June, and I spent weeks finding alternatives. Finally I got one, and it worked for me very well for more than 2 months. However, just 3 days after you published this damn article, it got killed too! You are effectively helping the evil authority to dig up and kill good tools!???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Damn it!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;


	</content>



</entry>
<entry>
	<title>Comment 7</title>

	<id>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_7/</id>

	<link href="http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/Ten_Things_to_Look_for_in_a_Circumvention_Tool/comment_7/"/>

	<author><name>phobos</name></author>





	<updated>2011-04-05T12:07:59Z</updated>
	<published>2010-09-23T12:07:59Z</published>

	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	We are improving tor all of the time.  I feel your angst, but the lack of details doesn&#39;t help solve the problem.  Have you tried bridges?  What errors do you get?  What country are you in that is blocking Tor?

	</content>



</entry>

</feed>
