<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" >
<channel>
<title>archive.torproject.org is now live</title>
<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/</link>
<description>The Tor Blog</description>
<item>

	<title>Chuck Filson (not verified): Comment 1</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Chuck Filson (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_1/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_1/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 06:31:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:40Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>Both &lt;a href=&quot;http://tor-node.goodeid.com:8080/&quot; title=&quot;http://tor-node.goodeid.com:8080/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://tor-node.goodeid.com:8080/&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://tor-node.goodeid.com:8443/&quot; title=&quot;https://tor-node.goodeid.com:8443/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://tor-node.goodeid.com:8443/&lt;/a&gt; are also online.
</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 2</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_2/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_2/</link>

	<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 06:31:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:41Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, I downloaded the latest version of tor bundle but it seems it doesnt work like the way it used to. about 3 months ago, tor allowed me to use exitnodes so I could use tor in very useful way.. thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but after I downloaded a new version of tor around this july, I can&#39;t get tor,torrc file worked for foxyproxy. coz when I added exitnodes in torrc file, vidila didn&#39;t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;uhm.. I&#39;m sorry I&#39;m not so good at this technological process so I need your help.&lt;br /&gt;
Would you help me to get this tor working like the way it used to before?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;many thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous (not verified): Comment 3</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_3/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_3/</link>

	<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 06:31:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:42Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Hello&lt;br /&gt;
Please  Help&lt;br /&gt;
As you know in china the blocked Youtube i download  tor-im-browser-1.2.6_zh-CN, now it is working very good but the video ca not be played and remain the same message&lt;br /&gt;
I downloaded and install the lst version of flashplayer and i set preference in Torbutton (uncheck the fist choise in security propreties (stop compnent while using Tor)&lt;br /&gt;
but  the problem remain the  same  no video played&lt;br /&gt;
Please  help&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous (not verified): Comment 4</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_4/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_4/</link>

	<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 06:31:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:43Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/torbutton/faq.html.en#noflash&quot; title=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/torbutton/faq.html.en#noflash&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://www.torproject.org/torbutton/faq.html.en#noflash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t view videos on YouTube and other Flash-based sites. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YouTube and similar sites require third party browser plugins such as Flash. Plugins operate independently from Firefox and can perform activity on your computer that ruins your anonymity. This includes but is not limited to: completely disregarding proxy settings, querying your local IP address, and storing their own cookies. It is possible to use a LiveCD or VMWare-based solution such as Tor VM or Incognito that creates a secure, transparent proxy to protect you from proxy bypass, however issues with local IP address discovery and Flash cookies still remain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not concerned about being tracked by these sites (and sites that try to unmask you by pretending to be them), and are unconcerned about your local censors potentially noticing you visit them, you can enable plugins by going into the Torbutton Preferences-&amp;gt;Security Settings-&amp;gt;Dynamic Content tab and unchecking &quot;Disable plugins during Tor usage&quot; box. If you do this without Tor VM, Incognito or appropriate firewall rules, we strongly suggest you at least use NoScript to block plugins. You do not need to use the NoScript per-domain permissions if you check the Apply these restrictions to trusted sites too option under the NoScript Plugins preference tab. In fact, with this setting you can even have NoScript allow Javascript globally, but still block all plugins until you click on their placeholders in a page. We also recommend Better Privacy in this case to help you clear your Flash cookies.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>dandin1 (not verified): Comment 5</title>
	<dcterms:creator>dandin1 (not verified)</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_5/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_5/</link>

	<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 06:31:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:44Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Since Tor disables Flash, you must manually download the video.  A small script is available that automatically does it for you:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://googlesystem.blogspot.com/2008/04/download-youtube-videos-as-mp4-files.html&quot; title=&quot;http://googlesystem.blogspot.com/2008/04/download-youtube-videos-as-mp4-files.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://googlesystem.blogspot.com/2008/04/download-youtube-videos-as-mp4-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Go to that page and right-click on &quot;get youtube video&quot;, then click &quot;Add as bookmark&quot;.&lt;br /&gt;
On any youtube page, you can click that bookmark to download the video.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 6</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_6/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_6/</link>

	<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 06:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:45Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being censored is a very painful experience, not that I can&#39;t live without facebook or dailymotion or youtube.&lt;br /&gt;
But I want to be able to choose.&lt;br /&gt;
Tor gives me this possibility, for free, and for that I am thankful.&lt;br /&gt;
But at the same time it restricts me and it acts like censorship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes I understand that Flash and Java are potentially leading to leak personnal informations that could serve the authorities to increase their FW.&lt;br /&gt;
But what&#39;s the point if I can&#39;t see a video when the main reason why I use Tor IS to access EASILY youtube? I don&#39;t wish to spend time configuring again, and again Firefox to be able to visualize a youtube video. It&#39;s supposed to be a relaxing time, not a &quot;fixing problem time&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me it appears exactly in the same way as the control chinese govt is trying to impose on me. Your reasons are different, the result is the same.&lt;br /&gt;
I can&#39;t see Youtube videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Youtube is ipso facto THE interface used everywhere for video references from facebook friends posting their preferences, to economical or scientific conferences. They are a monopoly already. I can question it. Meanwhile, I do the choice to use it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please, wouldn&#39;t it possible to add simplicity to the process and let your user access youtube video without to feel punished? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for any answers and your attention.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 7</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_7/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_7/</link>

	<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 06:31:46 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:46Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Well I found a solution, very easy actually...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that I didn&#39;t use Firefox before is a part of the problem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though I followed the rules and unchecked the boxes in the Tor Add-on menu it still didn&#39;t work.&lt;br /&gt;
You&#39;ll have to start Firefox without Tor first, install the Flash player, restart Firefox  and then only then, launch Tor with your Firefox session still open. The flash player being installed and recognized before, it&#39;s all fine and it will work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course for most of the code lovers that are behind Tor, this is ridiculously simple, at the point that they don&#39;t really care to inquire or even think we poor things only used IE or some other Microsoft interface to surf before to be saved (just kidding, nothing serious)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I must say that some answers that provoke your deep admiration with all the code implied (see this &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/testing-tor-browser-bundle-120dev&quot; title=&quot;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/testing-tor-browser-bundle-120dev&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://blog.torproject.org/blog/testing-tor-browser-bundle-120dev&lt;/a&gt; ), just make me laugh out loud (now that I can acess youtube and others)&lt;br /&gt;
But I do acknowledge your deep concern for our freedom. So big and warm thank you [dear nerds]&lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 8</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_8/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_8/</link>

	<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 06:31:47 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:47Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>&lt;p&gt;Not being enough of a nerd, I cannot pretend to understand the coding implied in this fix, but I can tell you it doesn&#39;t seem to work for me.  My main intent in using Tor at the moment is to watch videos that other countries have barred me from watching--I started using it in China, for obvious reasons, but now I just want to watch youku videos that are blocked in my region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve probably downloaded and installed flash a dozen times in the past half an hour, and when I try to do it with torbutton toggled on enabled it encounters an error and doesn&#39;t install correctly, and when I do it with torbutton toggled off there is no indication that I&#39;ve done so once I toggle it on again.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m not concerned with my activities being monitored--anyone who wants to learn what they can from my video selection is welcome to infer what they will from my choice of Disney movies.  I am interested in learning a little more about the underlying mechanics of tor and its accouterments, and would very much like to figure out how to use it to watch flash-based videos within the week.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve tried unchecking the &quot;disable plugins during tor usage&quot; setting to no avail, and now I&#39;ve tried this download flash-restart firefox-THEN open tor fix and still am Alice in Wonderlandless.  Can&#39;t anyone help me, please? &lt;/p&gt;

</description>


</item>
<item>

	<title>Anonymous: Comment 9</title>
	<dcterms:creator>Anonymous</dcterms:creator>


	<guid>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_9/</guid>

	<link>http://localhost/jmtodaro/tor/blog/posts/archive_torproject_org_is_now_live/comment_9/</link>

	<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:31:48 -0600</pubDate>
	<dcterms:modified>2011-04-05T11:31:48Z</dcterms:modified>

	<description>When I try to download a video from a .onion site, I receive a warning that I am using an external application when I download, and that this may unmask me. What are my risks that someone may be able to watch what I am doing when I download from a .onion site while tor is enabled? My browser is firefox with the torbutton plugin.
</description>


</item>

</channel>
</rss>
